Guide to the School of Forestry, Yale University, Alumni Records and Records of the Yale Forest Club
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Forestry, Yale University, alumni records and records of the Yale Forest Club
1900-2003
RU 45
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
The records consist of financial records, minutes, and officers' books for the Yale Forest Club and School of Forestry alumni. Also included is a Yale School of Forestry register, 1900-1907. Also included are records and a videotape documenting the 2003 alumni weekend.
Yale Forest Club
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 24-G (YRG 24-G), Records of Yale School of Forestry student, alumni, and support organizations.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1982; and gift of Kathleen Schomaker, 2004.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by subject and record type.
Biographical / Historical
The Yale Forestry Club was established during the 1904-1905 school year. The Yale School of Forestry became the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies in 1972.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of financial records, minutes, and officers' books for the Yale Forest Club and School of Forestry alumni. Also included is a Yale School of Forestry register, 1900-1907. Also included are records and a videotape documenting the 2003 alumni weekend.
Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Videotapes; Yale Forestry Club; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University. School of Forestry
- Records, 1900-1968; Accession 1982-A-020
  - Alumni Dues: ledger, 1939-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 2)
  - Checking record, First National Bank & Trust Co., 1951-1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1908, Yale Forest School, Book of the Secretary (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Yale Forest Club
    - Minutes, 1937-1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Petty cash book, 1931-1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Secretary's book, 1902-1904 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer's book, 1931-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Yale Forest School register, 1900-1907 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Records and videotape, 2003; Accession 2005-A-050
  - Records (Box 1)
  - Videotape (VHS) (Box 2)